<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Blind Guys Paradise</title>
    <link>http://Blind-Guy-Paradise.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Blind Guys Paradise</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 18:26:47 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://Blind-Guy-Paradise.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://Blind-Guy-Paradise.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 16:21:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://Blind-Guy-Paradise.org/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a passionate software engineer with a strong interest in open source development. I am currently a Google Summer of Code 2023 student developer with the PostgreSQL Global Development Group. In my spare time, I enjoy playing video games, watching old irrelevant Movies, and staring into the vast nothingness.
Repos / Projects Here&amp;rsquo;s a sample of some dumb stuff I work on.
Postgres-extension-tutorial - An easy-to-follow tutorial with clear examples because the barrier for entry is prohibitive for new contributors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSoC’23 at PostgreSQL (Biweekly Report 4)</title>
      <link>http://Blind-Guy-Paradise.org/posts/week4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 18:26:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://Blind-Guy-Paradise.org/posts/week4/</guid>
      <description>Introduction:
Welcome to another update on my Google Summer of Code (GSoC) project, where I&amp;rsquo;ve been making significant strides in Postgres extension development. From Day 43 to Day 56, I focused on finalizing the tutorial content, working on sample extensions, addressing issues, and incorporating official documentation references. In this blog post, I will share the key highlights of my progress during this phase of the project.
Github Repository: https://github.com/IshaanAdarsh/Postgres-extension-tutorial</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSoC’23 at PostgreSQL (Biweekly Report 3)</title>
      <link>http://Blind-Guy-Paradise.org/posts/week3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 18:26:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://Blind-Guy-Paradise.org/posts/week3/</guid>
      <description>Introduction:
Welcome to another update on my Google Summer of Code (GSoC) project, where I&amp;rsquo;ve been diving deeper into the world of Postgres extension development. In this blog post, I&amp;rsquo;ll share the highlights of my progress from Day 29 to Day 42, including my exploration of PGXN and PGXS, the improvement of the Minimum Viable Product (MVP), content organization, and my focus on regression testing and extension management.
PGXN and PGXS:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSoC’23 at PostgreSQL (Biweekly Report 2)</title>
      <link>http://Blind-Guy-Paradise.org/posts/week2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 18:26:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://Blind-Guy-Paradise.org/posts/week2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction:
Welcome to another update on my Google Summer of Code (GSoC) project, where I&amp;rsquo;ve been diving deep into the world of Postgres extension development. Over the past two weeks (Day 14 to Day 28), I&amp;rsquo;ve made significant progress, overcoming challenges, refining tutorial content, and organizing my repository. In this blog post, I will share the highlights of my journey, from restructuring tutorials to mastering the Makefile and everything in between.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSoC’23 at PostgreSQL (Biweekly Report 1)</title>
      <link>http://Blind-Guy-Paradise.org/posts/week1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 18:26:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://Blind-Guy-Paradise.org/posts/week1/</guid>
      <description>I got accepted for Google Summer of Code 2023 with PostgreSQL . I&amp;rsquo;m stoked to be working on a project where I&amp;rsquo;ll be creating an easy-to-follow tutorial on writing Postgres extension under the guidance of awesome mentors.
My Project:
GSoC Proposal Project Page Mentors: Jimmy Angelakos, David Wheeler As a GSoC student working on a Postgres extension project, my first two weeks have been a journey filled with diverse experiences. I began by meeting my mentors who provided valuable insights into the project&amp;rsquo;s timeline, deliverables, and the scope of possibilities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
